Guide to the Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
- Series VI: Burlington, Vermont
  - "To the Editor". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Oct. 24 - 31, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Article Appears On Same Page As Previous Entry) -- Author: Sanders, Bernard.
  - "Barre, Too, Lays Claim to a Socialist Mayor - in 1916". The Burlington Free Press., Nov. 1, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Taylor, John.
  - "Inside Track". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Oct. 3 - 10, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Sidewalk Plows Drifting Along, Waiting for Snow". The Burlington Free Press., Dec. 27, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: MacKay, Scott.
  - "Coalition Asks City to Buy House for Battered Women". The Burlington Free Press., Jun. 22, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Burlington Zoners OK Plans For Battered Women's Shelter". The Burlington Free Press., Jun. 6, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Eley, Rob.
  - "Women's Shelters Awarded $15,000 in State Grants", Jun. 30, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Article Appears On Same Page As Previous Entry)
  - "School Sales Prompt...". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Mar. 26, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Incomplete Article)
  - "Aldermen Will Discuss Adams School". The Burlington Free Press., Apr. 8, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Additional Copy - Article Appears On Back Side of Previous Entry) -- Author: Peck, Jodie.
  - "Confusion Over Adams School". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Apr. 23 - 30, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Article Appears On Same Page As Previous Entry) -- Author: Greene, Diana.
  - "Peace March Arrives". The Burlington Free Press., Unknown (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page.
  - "Mayor Meets Buddhists". The Burlington Free Press., Apr. 9, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Untitled Commentary. The Vermont Vanguard Press., Jul. 30 - Aug. 6, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Mamis, Joshua.
  - "Vermonters Form Coalition to Take On Reagan". The Burlington Free Press., Apr. 4, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Karvelas, David.
  - "Groups Back Peace Coalition". The Burlington Free Press., Apr. 13, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Local Leaders Weave Some New Safety Nets". The Vermont Vanguard Press., May 21 - 28, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Center Offers Workshops In Community Organizing". The Burlington Free Press., Jul. 8, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Unions Joining Anti-Reagan Rally". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Aug. 27 - Sept. 3, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Mueller, Dian.
  - "State of the People: Coalition to Hold Hearings Tonight". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Sept. 17 - 24, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Burlington, Barre Hold Hearings On Impact of Federal Cutbacks". The Burlington Free Press., Sept. 10, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Hockert-Lotz, Nelson and Taylor, John.
  - "Small Showing At Ground Zero". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Apr. 23 - 30, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Valicenti, Trish.
  - "Sanders Calls for Disarmament Support". The Burlington Free Press., Apr. 23, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Article Appears On Same Page As Previous Entry) -- Author: Palmer, Ezra.
  - "Civil Defense Chiefs Struggle With Plans For Nuclear Survival". The Burlington Free Press., May 14 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Melvin, Don.
  - "400 Join Hands, Voices In City Hall Park Rally To Protest KKK Racism". The Burlington Free Press., May 16 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Special Issues on Ballots in Chittenden County". The Burlington Free Press., Nov. 2, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Incomplete Article) -- Author: Donoghue, Mike.
  - "El Salvador on Ballot in Burlington, St. A.". The Burlington Free Press., Oct. 29, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "El Salvador Issue Could Face Vote At Town Meetings". The Burlington Free Press., Dec. 15, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Activists Protest Renewed Military Aid to El Salvador". The Burlington Free Press., Jan. 26, 1983 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Sorensen, Eric.
  - "After-School Funds Receive a 'No' Vote From City Aldermen". The Burlington Free Press., Jun. 4, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Radical Economists Offer Ways To Get Involved in Government". The Burlington Free Press., Jun. 6, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Reilly, John.
  - "Park Concert". The Burlington Free Press., Jul. 16, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Untitled Commentary. The Vermont Vanguard Press., Jul. 16, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "People's Circus Comes to Town". The Burlington Free Press., Jul. 31 (1982?) (Box 9)
  - "Inside Track". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Jul. 2 - 9, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Acid Rain Drops Keep Falling...". The Burlington Free Press., Jul. 23, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Mayor Asks Businessmen To Back Youth Programs". The Burlington Free Press., Jul. 20, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Tedford, Ted.
  - "Connecting Kids with Community". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Aug. 13 - 20, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Trahan, Paula.
  - "Spring Fling Crowds Appear Less Destructive". The Burlington Free Press., May, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Comedian Youngman Gets The Red-Carpet Treatment But His Sore Feet No Joke". The Burlington Free Press., May 27 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Green, Susan.
  - Untitled. The Vermont Vanguard Press., Jul. 23 - 30, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "New Parties Blossom in Bad Times". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Sept. 23 - 30, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "In Rutland, Mayor's Story Reads Like Sanders' Saga". The Burlington Free Press., May 17 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Berney, Louis.
  - "Assessing Sanders: How Goes Burlington With a Socialist In City Hall?". The Vermont Vanguard Press., Dec. 31, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 4 pages. -- Author: Bookchin, Debbie.
  - "Preliminary OK Given To Parade Ordinance". The Burlington Free Press., Dec. 23, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Paquette Drops Lawsuit Against Vanguard Press". The Burlington Free Press., Jan. 1, 1983 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Braun, William H.
  - "Senate OKs Burlington's Water Bonds". The Burlington Free Press., Mar. 25 (Year Unknown) (Box 9)
  - "Clavelle Says Advisory Panel Proposal Not a New Idea". The Burlington Free Press., Oct. 21, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Money, Criminal Justice at Top of Legislative Agenda". The Burlington Free Press., Nov. 9, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Montpelier Searches for New Tax Sources". The Burlington Free Press., Nov. 11, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Lindner, Will.
  - "Mayor's Group Could Serve as Useful Lobbyists". The Burlington Free Press., Nov. 30, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Small City Mayors Will Hold Meeting About Lobbying Effort"., Dec. 10, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "3 Small City Mayors Decide To Join Forces". The Burlington Free Press., Dec. 12, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. (Article Appears On Same Page As Previous Entry) -- Author: Cowperthwait, Richard.
  - "G.O.P. Governor Urges Vermont Jobs Program". The New York Times., Jan. 24, 1983 (Box 9)
  - " ' 82 Legislative Session Marked by Productivity". The Burlington Free Press., Dec. 28, 1982 (Box 9)
  - "Program Benefits Strained: ANFC Meeting Fewer Needs". The Burlington Free Press., Dec. 29, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Davis, Neil.
  - "Morse 'Fine-Tunes' Democrats Our of Committee Seats". The Burlington Free Press., Jan. 8, 1983 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Sline, Deborah.
  - "Vermonters to Give Views by Telephone To Senate Hearing". The Burlington Free Press., Feb. 5, 1983 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Springer, Katherine.
  - The Progressive Coalition: Vermont's grass-roots political organization working for social change. Published by: The Vermont Progressive Coalition., June 20, 1905 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 1 page. Double-Sided Newsletter.
  - "Burlington loves Bernie". In These Times., Mar. 23 - 29, 1983 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 6 pages. (Complete Copy) -- Author: Moberg, David.
  - "Burlington loves Bernie". In These Times., Mar. 23 - 29, 1983 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; Miscellaneous & General section. Photocopy. 4 pages. (Complete Copy) -- Author: Moberg, David.
  - "Burlington loves Bernie". In These Times., Mar. 23 - 29, 1983 (Box 9)
  - The 1995 Burlington Consolidated Plan for Housing and Community Development. Prepared by: The Burlington Community and Economic Development Office, Jun. 1995 (Box 9, Folder x)
    Bound Copy of The 1995 Burlington Consolidated Plan for Housing and Community Development; 244 total pages. (Some pages Not Numbered or Out of Order)
- Series VII. Chicago and Harold Washington
  - Office of the Mayor. Chicago Central Area Plan (Redraft). Prepared by Chicago Central Are Committee. Chicago., July 17, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Photocopy. 85 pages.
  - Office of the Mayor. Chicago Central Area Plan (Draft for Review). Prepared by Chicago Central Are Committee. Chicago., May 26, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Photocopy. 96 pages.
  - Committee to Re-Elect Mayor Washington. A Working Chicago. Chicago, June 9, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Committee to Re-Elect Mayor Washington. Mayor Washington's Action Agenda for Chicago's Future: 1987-1991. Chicago, June 9, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Original Pamphlet. Photocopy. 16 pages.
  - Office of the Mayor. Mayor's Press Office. The Washington Administration at Mid-Term. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Banking on It: Cash Flowing to Credit-Starved Areas." Chicago Sun-Times., Mar. 8, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Photocopy of Article. 1 page.
  - Business Loss or Balanced Growth: Industrial Displacement in Chicago. Prepared by New City YMCA: Economic Development Unit, Research and Development Division: Department of Economic Development of City of Chicago, Center for Urban Economic Development at University of Illinois at Chicago., Aug., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Original Bound Publication. Photocopy. 52 pages. -- Author: Ducharme, Donna, Robert Giloth, and Lynn McCormick.
  - Office of the Mayor. Chicago Development Plan. Chicago., May, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Original Bound Publication. Photocopy (2 copies). 60 pages.
  - Local Economic Development in Chicago, 1983-1987: The Reform Efforts of Mayor Harold Washington. PhD Dissertation. Cornell University, Ithaca. Correspondence and Notes., May, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Original Bound Copy. 257 pages. -- Author: Reardon, Ken.
  - Faith Based Community Development with Emphasis on Chicago: Bibliography. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Faith in the Community: Churches, synagogues and mosques are rebuilding neighborhoods and redefining organizing." A special focus of The Neighborhood Works: Building Alternative Visions for the City. Pp2, 16-26., Sept./Oct., 1996. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Photocopy of Article. 6 pages.
  - "Can Churches Save America?" U.S. News & World Report. Pp. 46-53., Sept. 9, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Photocopy of Article. 4 pages. -- Author: Sharipo Joseph and Andrea Wright.
  - "Ministers Who Work Around The Flock: Many Companies Hire Chaplains as Counselors." The New York Times, Business Day. Pp. D1, D20., Oct. 3, 1996. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Photocopy of Article. 1 page. -- Author: Feder, Barnaby J.
  - Real Hope in Chicago: the Incredible Story of How the Gospel is Transforming a Chicago Neighborhood. Grand Rapids, MI: Zondervan Publishing House. Chapter 9: "Investing in People." pp. 115-124. Chapter 11: "A Piece of the Pound." pp. 137-146., June 17, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Photocopy. 9 pages. -- Author: Gordon, Wayne L. and Randall Frame.
  - Chicago's Industry Task Forces: Joint Problem-Solving for Local Economic Development., Jan., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 12 pages. -- Author: Lerner, Joshua, Robert Giloth, and Stephen Alexander.
  - Center for Urban Economic Development, The University of Illinois at Chicago and the Chicago Historical Society. The Washington Administration Neighborhood and Economic Development Papers: A Proposal to Establish an Archive. Submitted to the Chicago Community Trust., Oct., 1988. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Committee to Elect Harold Washington Mayor of Chicago. The Washington Papers: A Commitment to Chicago, A Commitment to You. Prepared under the direction of The Research and Issues Committee Washing for Mayor Campaign. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Photocopy. 52 pages.
  - "Downtown Building Fee Gets Nudge." Chicago Tribune., June 29, 1984. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Shanker, Thom.
  - Map of Chicago Downtown Development: 1979-1984. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Department of Economic Development. Chicago's Enterprise Zones: Informational Booklet. Chicago. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Department of Economic Development. Cooperation for Survival and Growth: New Designs for Apparel Manufacturing In Chicago. Prepared by Mayor Washington's Apparel and Fashion Industry Task Force Final Report., Mar., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Department of Economic Development. Building on the Basics: The Final Report of the Mayor's Task Force on Steel and Southeast Chicago. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Bibliographies: Newspapers, Books, Journals. Correspondence to Pierre Clavel, from Joan Fitzgerald, University of Ohio (August 10, 1990) with her Bibliography. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Photocopies. Several copies. 72 pages total. -- Author: Clavel, Pierre
  - "Democratic Populism in the USA: The Case of Playskool and Chicago. Cities. 3 (1): 72-74., Feb., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Photocopies. 4 pages. -- Author: Mier, Robert.
  - "Strategic Planning and the Pursuit of Reform, Economic Development, and Equity." APA Journal. pp. 299-309., Summer, 1986. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 10 pages. -- Author: Mier, Robert, Kari J. Moe, and Irene Sherr.
  - McCarron, John. Chicago Tribune Articles. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "'Reform' Takes Costly Toll.", Aug. 28, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Photocopy of Article. 3 pages. -- Author: McCarron, John.
    - "Slum Owner's Brother Tries to Sack Bears Stadium.", Aug. 29, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Photocopy of Article. 2 pages. -- Author: McCarron, John.
    - "Memory of Early Days leaves Urban Renewal With Cross to Bear." (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "Votes give CHA Slums a Reason For Life.", Aug. 30, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Photocopy of Article. 4 pages. -- Author: McCarron, John.
    - "Blue Collar Dream Skews City Policy.", Aug. 31, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "When a Vacant Factory Holds More Appeal Than New Condos." (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Photocopy of Article. 1 page. -- Author: McCarron, John.
    - "Shiller Guards Against Uptown Progress.", Sept. 1, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "2 Viewpoints on the Future of Uptown." (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "On West Side, it's Ald. Henrys Way or No Way.", Sept. 2, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "City Leaders Blew School Reform Chances.", Sept. 4, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "The Timid City.", Sept. 4, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Strong, James. Chicago Tribune Articles. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - "Neighborhoods Try To Tap into Business.", Feb. 13, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Photocopy of Article. 1 page. -- Author: Strong, James.
    - "Council Makes Pact on Repair Bonds." (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Photocopy of Article. 2 pages. -- Author: Strong, James.
  - "Challenging Chicago's Growth Machine: A Preliminary Report on the Washington Administration." International Journal of Urban and Regional Research. 11(3): 351-362, Sept., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Photocopy of Journal. 11 pages. -- Author: Bennett, Larry, Gregory D. Squires, Kathleen McCourt and Philip Nyden.
  - "Downtown vs. Neighborhoods." Chicago Tribune., Aug. 30, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Hyde Park Citizen., Nov. 19-22, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Original Newspaper Publication (in full). 24 pages.
  - "Spatial Change and Social Justice: Alternative Economic Development in Chicago." pp. 181-208. Economic Restructuring and Political Response, Robert A. Beauregard, Ed. Sage: Beverly Hills, CA., June 11, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Photocopy -- Author: Giloth, Robert P. and Robert Mier.
  - Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning. Rebuilding Nature's Metropolis Growth and Sustainability in the 21st Century. Preliminary Program. 41st Annual Conference, Chicago., Oct. 21-24, 1999. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Original Bound Publication. 87 pages.
  - Office of the Mayor Harold Washington. News Release. Mayor Proposes New Neighborhood Improvement Program., July 19, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 28)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 17 pages.
  - "Mayor Names Panel to Boost Neighborhoods." Chicago Sun Times., Sept. 30, 1984. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Photocopy of Article. 2 pages. -- Author: Johnson, Dirk.
  - "Town mulls 'impact' fee on developers.", Oct. 10, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Photocopy of Article. 1 page. -- Author: Papajohn, George.
  - "Harold Washington's Balancing Act." Chicago, pp, 180-207., Apr. 1985. (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Photocopy of Article. 9 pages. -- Author: Kelly, Brian.
  - "Why I Was Chosen and Who he Mayor Chose." The Department of Planning under Harold Washington. pp. 222-281. (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Photocopy. 61 pages. -- Author: Hollander, Elizabeth.
  - "'Impact Fees' Debated in Booming Naperville.", Nov. 17, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Photocopy of Article. 2 pages. -- Author: Kerch, Steve.
  - Chicago's Future: The People's Choice.Chicago, IL., Sept., 1985. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Photocopy. 41 pages. -- Author: Klutznick, Thomas J.
  - Planning is a Mirror of Western Societies in the Coming Decades: The Case of the New American Metropolitan Planning. Paper presented at the 1985 IPSA World Congress in Paris, July 15-20. Session III.2. Planning and the Limits of Governmental Regulation. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Photocopy. 24 pages. -- Author: Kreukels, Anton M. J.
  - "$600,000 study says Chicago." Chicago Sun Times., Oct. 26, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Photocopy of Article. 1 page. -- Author: Golden, Jr. Harry.
  - Crains Chicago Business Articles. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Author: Goozner, Merrill.
    - "Neighborhoods to get boost in City's 1984 Spending Plan.", Dec. 5, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - "Touchy development tax stirs city interest." (Box 8, Folder 37)
      Photocopy of Article. 1 page
    - "City earmarks funds for neighborhoods aid." (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - "Six-year building boom in and near the Loop." Chicago Sun Times., Aug. 21, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Photocopy of Article. 1 page -- Author: Gibons, Tom.
  - Developers on hold since Mayoral Race." Chicago Tribune., May 1, 1983. (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Photocopy of Article. 2 pages. -- Author: Washburn, Gary.
  - Provisional Outline and Chapter Titles: Economic Policy and Neighborhood Organization in Chicago, 1983-187. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Clavel, Pierre and Wim Wiewel.
  - "The Social Organization of a Land-Based Elite: The Case of the Failed Chicago 1992 World's Fair." Journal of Urban Affairs. 9(4): 305-324., June 9, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Photocopy of Journal. 10 pages. -- Author: Shlay, Anne B. and Robert Giloth.
  - The Center for Urban Economic Development, University of Illinois at Chicago. The Impact of the Federal and State Urban Development Action Grants (UDAG, IDAG) on Chicago: 1979-1986. Prepared for the Chicago 1992 Committee. (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Harvard on Halstead: Dilemmas of Neighborhood Advocacy in Academia. The Center for Urban Economic Development, University of Illinois at Chicago. Prepared for the Annual Meeting of the Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning, Atlanta., Nov., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    Original Bound Publication. 18 pages. -- Author: Wiewel, Wim.
  - Community Workshop on Economic Development Materials: Publications and Handouts. (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Monthly News & Notes., June, 1987. (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Community Enterprise. The Community Workshop on Economic Development Newsletter., Summer, 1986. (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Annual Report 1986., June 8, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      3 copies. Bound Original Publication. 3 pages.
    - About CWED Handouts. (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Original Handouts. 4 pages.
  - Economic Home Cooking': An Action Guide for Congregations on Community Economic Development. Community Workshop on Economic Development. Chicago, IL., Sept., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 45)
    Original Bound Publication. 46 pages. -- Author: Zalent, Kim.
  - Chicago United Economic Development Task Force. Economic Development: A Proposal Prepared for the Chicago Economic Development Commission., June 7, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 18 pages.
  - Chicago's Economy: Washington vs. Byrne. Summary Data. (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Latino Business In Chicago: Obstacles, Opportunities and Directions For Growth. Prepared by Research and Training Associates and Research and Development Division, Department of Economic Development, City of Chicago., July, 1986. (Box 8, Folder 48)
    Original Bound Publication. 33 pages. -- Author: Triana, Armando and Ricardo Tostado.
  - Monitoring Chicago's Industrial Revenue Bond Performance: 1977-1984. A Chicago Working Paper. Prepared by Research and Development Division, Chicago Department of Economic Development., July, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    Original Bound Publication. 52 pages. -- Author: Clemons, Gwendolyn, Robert Giloth, and Ricardo Tostado.
  - Navy Pier Task Force Information. (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Mayor's Navy Pier Task Force. Window on the Future. Final Report of the Mayor's Navy Task Force. (Box 8, Folder 50)
      Original Bound Publication. 85 pages.
    - Mayor's Navy Pier Task Force. Window on the Future. Final Report Summary of the Mayor's Navy Task Force. (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence. To Community Organization, From Robert Mier, Commissioner, Department of Economic Development, City of Chicago. Re: Update on Navy Pier Task Force., Sept. 11, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 50)